

Charles Chuka Osegbue

Lagos State, Nigeria. +2348103442322, +2347019227318

osegbuecharles.com - osegbuecharles@gmail.com

Professional Sumary

OSEGBUE CHARLES

Well trained Computer Scientist with mid to high level experience in information technology. Areas of expertise include web design, software development, IT personnel and computer maintenance. Enthusiastic programmer well versed in a range of e-solutions and technologies.

Education

○ BACHELOR OF SCIENCE(COMPUTER SCIENCE)

2016 - 2020

Augustine University Ilara Epe, Lagos, Nigeria

- First Class Honors
- Best Graduating Student Faculty of Science 2020
- Pioneer President Faculty of Science Student Association (FACUSSA),
 2019/2020 Academic Session
- Deans list Student for 3 years in a row
- Project Work: Clinic Management System

HIGH SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

2010 - 2016

St. Vincent Catholic School Bammeke ShaSha, Lagos, Nigeria

- Senior Prefect (Head Boy)
- Set Valecdictorian
- CowbellPedia Maths Competition
- Milo Basketball Competition
- St. Agnes Fine arts competition

Professional Experience

SENIOR DEVELOPER

2019 - Present

Wine Red 🖁, Lagos, Nigeria

- Lead in Custom Website Development
- Delegate tasks to the 4 members of the development team and provide counsel on all aspects of the project.
- Supervise the assessment of all graphic materials in order to ensure quality and accuracy of the design
- Oversee the efficient use of production project budgets.

August,2017 - Oct,2017, August,2018 - Oct,2018

CCOTTECH, Lagos, Nigeria

- Assisting Senior It Personnel in monitoring servers
- Answering phone calls for the It department
- Assisting Senior It Personnel in Server Installation and relocation
- Clipping cat 6 cables
- Assisting Senior It Personnel in installing new thin clients for staffs
- Maintenance and repair of thin clients, desktops and printers

JUNIOR DEVELOPER (INTERN)

April,2018 - Oct,2018

Fountain of Love Systems, GM PLAZA, Lagos, Nigeria

- Testing and Debugging of projects made by senior developers
- Setting Milestone Progress for Projects
- Creating User Manual on Softwares for Clients
- Presenting and explaining Software functionality to clients
- Building Python Based Applications for Sensitive Projects

Professional Skills

- Fast Learner
 - Web Design
 - Team Player
 - Good Communication Skills
 - Critical Thinking

- Adaptive Worker
 - Computer literate
 - Research and Analysis
 - Analytical Skill

Certifications

- 1. Python 3 Tutorial Course(May,2017) at Sololearn, www.sololearn.com
- 2. C++ Tutorial Course(April,2018) at Sololearn, www.sololearn.com
- 3. HTML Fundamental Course(May,2018) at Sololearn, www.sololearn.com
- 4. Java Tutorial Course(May,2018) at Sololearn, www.sololearn.com

Referees

Dr. Grace Oletu

Assistant Professor in Software Engineering, School of Information Technology & Computing, at American University of Nigeria,

Yola

+2349051651274

graceoletu@gmail.com

Dr. Ayodele Lasisi

Senior Lecturer Computer Science, at Augustine University Ilara Epe,

Lagos

+2348140633805

lasisiayodele@yahoo.com

Dr. Raphael Ikechukwu Izuora

Corporate Services Manager at Nigeria Communications Commission,

Abuja

+2348157777909

eyekingdazle@gmail.com

Mr. Adeagbo Tolulope

Senior Developer Fountain of Love Systems Sangotedo, Lagos

+2347034247018

tolusoft2010@yahoo.com

A copy of this resume can be found at osegbuecharles.com/cv